<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>krenz</title>
 <link href="https://krenz.co/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="https://krenz.co/"/>
 <updated>2020-04-29T10:05:12+02:00</updated>
 <id>https://krenz.co</id>
 <author>
   <name>Eric Krenz</name>
   <email>krenzew@mail.uc.edu</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Hello World</title>
   <link href="https://krenz.co/blog/hello-world/"/>
   <updated>2020-04-11T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <id>https://krenz.co/blog/hello-world</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/posts/rothenburg-plonlein.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; style=&quot;margin-top: 1rem; margin-bottom: 2rem;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;float: right; margin-top: -2rem; margin-bottom: -1rem; font-size: .75rem; &quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Rothenburg, Germany 2020&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an example blog post that I threw together as an example of what a piece of literature would look like in this site’s ever-growing encyclopedia of knowledge. I am not sure what the contents of this forum will contain yet, so I am going to let it form over time.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This novella will start as some of the first technical writings that I have created for fun. I want to share any thoughts, learnings, photos, tools, or programs that I am interested in. I will continue learning various different topics, so writing these posts to explain different topics will help with the topic’s retention. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a big fan of puzzles. I enjoy finding order in chaos. Writing will help explain complicated concepts in ways that everyone can understand. I want to improve myself by being able to better explain complicated topics to others. The more I do something, I would hope to get better at it.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stay-hungry-stay-foolish&quot;&gt;“Stay Hungry, Stay Foolish”&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever since I first saw Steve Job’s Stanford commencement speach on YouTube, those words stuck with me. Those are words that I currently live by, not only for my preferences towards good food and comedies. I am curious by nature and will always continue to find ways to improve as a person. I picture myself learning and posting about many different topics, which could cover but are not limited to:
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tech and software&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Business practices&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finances and markets&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;US/World Travelling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Food
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If any of that sounds interesting, keep an eye out for more posts that I will be sharing. Cheers!
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. This post was made to be more light-hearted, comical, and slightly sarcastic. Try not read too deep into anything mentioned above.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
